Guide to the Collection of Aerial Photographs 1935-2001
Western Washington University, Center for Pacific Northwest Studies
- Aerial Photographs and Orthophotos, 1935-2000; Series II
  - Bluefield, Mercer County, West Virginia, 1968-10-21; DZG (Box 113)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: DZG-4JJ-5, 6, 7
  - Charleston, Kanawha County, West Virginia, 05-06-1057; AMD (Box 113)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: AMD-6R-160, 161, 162
  - Green Bay, Brown County, Wisconsin, 1967-09-02; BHL (Box 113)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: BHL-2HH-43 thru 46
  - Milwaukee, Milwaukee County, Wisconsin, 1963-07-29; WX (Box 113)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: WX-1DD-37 thru 40, 101 thru 103
  - Beloit, Rock County, Wisconsin, 1963-08-20; XA (Box 113)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: XA-81, 82, 83
  - Western Washington State, 1969 and 1970; NW-69; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Box 114)
  - Western Washington State - Thurston, King, Shohomish, Skagit, Island, Mason County, 1978; NW-C-76; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Box 114)
  - Cascades National Forests, Washington, 1979-09-13; 616030; United States. Dept. of Agriculture (Box 115)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 478-112 (3 copies) and 478-112 (1 copy)
  - Chehalis, Washington, 1980-07-27; GS-VEYV (Box 115)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-17 thru 1-87 (missing 1-46)
  - Chehalis, Washington, 1980-07-27; GS-VEYV (Box 115)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-90 thru 1-172 (missing 1-132)
  - Chehalis, Washington, 1980-07-27; GS-VEYV (Box 115)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-219 thru 1-240; 1-247 thru 1-257; 1-289 thru 1-306
  - Chehalis, Washington, 1980-09-03; GS-VEYV (Box 115)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2-2 thru 2-20; 2-27 thru 2-36; 2-52 thru 2-68; 2-77 thru 2-103
  - Chehalis, Washington, 1980-09-03; GS-VEYV (Box 115)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2-104 thru 2-116; 2-147 thru 2-176; 2-191 thru 2-206
  - Clallam County, Washington, 1981-07-04; OL-81; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Box 115)
  - Washington State, 1979-08-09; 626090 (Box 116)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: Various photo negatives
    626090 in multiple locations (photos and negs.).
  - Washington State, 1980-07-07; 626090 (Box 116)
  - Washington State, 1980-07-21; 626090 (Box 116)
  - Cle Elum Area, Kittitas County, Washington, 1966-10-31; REC-17-6-2 (Box 116)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-1 thru 1-130
  - Cowlitz County, Washington, 1964-09-11; ENJ (Box 117)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ENJ-1EE-2 thru 20; 23 thru 43; 52 thru 65; 94 thru 123
  - Cowlitz County, Washington, 1964-9-11 thru 1964-10-3; ENJ (Box 117)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ENJ-1EE-124 thru 157; 159 thru 164; 185 thru 211
  - Cowlitz County, Washington, 1964-09-11; ENJ (Box 117)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ENJ-2EE-1 thru 13; 39 thru 54; 75 thru 123
  - Cowlitz County, Washington, 1964-09-12; ENJ (Box 117)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ENJ-2EE-124 thru 166; 174 thru 200
  - Cowlitz County, Washington, 1964-09-12; ENJ (Box 117)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ENJ-2EE-201 thru 224; 238 thru 257; 259 thru 285
  - Cowlitz County, Washington, 1964-10-03; ENJ (Box 117)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: ENJ-3EE-4 thru 34; 50 thru 64
  - Alabama, PM; EH; HG; CPU; HO; BQE; HX (Box 118/1)
  - Arkansas, CCB; CFC; AVQ; COV; IC; BPT; EN; BPU; II; CZO; CEU; EK; EN; BPV; IQ; IH; BPW (Box 118/1)
  - Arizona, DUH; DHP; DHQ; DHP; CVK (Box 118/1)
  - Connecticut, DPD; CNE; CNF (Box 118/2)
  - Delaware, AHP; AHQ; AHN (Box 118/2)
  - Florida, IT; BUP; EEP; BUM; CTU; CPJ (Box 118/2)
  - Georgia, IZ; IW; ATG; ATW; ATH; ATI; EMX; KN; LN; EMZ; MA (Box 118/2)
  - Hawaii, EKL; EKQ; EKP (Box 118/2)
  - California, AAX; AAY; CVL; ABN; ABJ; ABL; AXJ; DRH; ABG; ABF; AXM; AXL; DDC; AXL; DRH; BTM; AXH; AAZ; BUT (Box 119/1)
  - Colorado, CWQ; YH; AIM; EKT; DXN; DYT; AIN; AXP; YK; AIG; DXO; CNG; CWT; EHZ (Box 119/1)
  - Hawaii, EKM; EKN (Box 119/2)
  - Iowa, BJW; SV; BKC; AJF; BKO; BKP (Box 119/2)
  - Idaho, DHT; DYU; CXN; CVO; CVP; CXO; CXS; DOS; DYW (Box 119/2)
  - Illinois, SG; BTW; BGQ; BFZ; BGM; ATCH; BWX; SJ; AR; BHA (Box 120/1)
  - Indiana, BWF; RJ; BFJ; RF; BFK; QY; BFP; QU (Box 120/1)
  - Kansas, CHG; CHE; AZJ; CCS; ZL; DHB; AYE (Box 120/1)
  - Kentucky, BUG; AFI; BUA; ALM; AFR; AFU; AGF; AED (Box 120/1)
  - Louisiana, CEF; CQE; CEF; CQF; DNI; CGG; CEZ; CJW; CTK; CEH; CEI; DRS; W; CQL; CEK; CTO (Box 120/1)
  - Massachusetts, DPU; DPN; DPM; DPL; DPO; DPP; CNI; DPS; DPV (Box 120/2)
  - Maryland, AGZ; ANJ; AMO; AHV; AHB (Box 120/2)
  - Maine, AHZ; AIA (Box 120/2)
  - Michigan, BVS; AIT; BDC; BVT; DVG; DVH; BDR; BDV; BWB; BWC (Box 120/2)
  - Minnesota, BRS (Box 120/2)
  - Missouri, BYL; UC; TP; BLJ; BLS; BLM; TR; BS; BZB; TY (Box 120/2)
  - Mississippi, AVF; ML; CZH; CZJ; NB; AVC; NM; CPR; AVL; NY (Box 120/2)
  - Montana, MV; MX; EHM; MS; NE; AZU; AZN; CXK; DWV; DWW; NC; DWY; ZW (Box 120/2)
  - North Carolina, AOI; AOC; BUS; ABW; ACQ; AJV; DKD; CSC (Box 121/1)
  - North Dakota, ZZ; CCQ; BAC; BAQ; AXE; BUL (Box 121/1)
  - New Hampshire, DXU; DXT; DQT; DXV; DQU; DQW (Box 121/1)
  - New Jersey, CMW; CMY; EAT; EAU (Box 121/1)
  - Nebraska, CAH; CBA; CBC; CBD; BNP; UO (Box 121/1)
  - New Mexico, EAV; EKH; CII; DFA; DFD; DFC; EKV; EAX (Box 121/1)
  - Nevada, DOP; ENI; DED (Box 121/1)
  - New York, CXE; EFD; CXG; ARP; CXH; ASA; ARE (Box 121/1)
  - Ohio, BBW; BVB; DU; PY; BCT; QG (Box 121/2)
  - Oklahoma, CZQ; CFN; CKH (Box 121/2)
  - Oregon, EOS; EFI; CNO; CHZ; DFM; DFO; AAE (Box 121/2)
  - Pennsylvania, AQH; APH; AQF; APD; AHG; AHN; AHH; AQS; APT; CMV (Box 121/2)
  - Rhode Island, DPI; DPJ (Box 121/2)
  - South Carolina, OT; BQN; CDU; S; CDV; GM; ATA; ATB; PK (Box 121/2)
  - Tennessee, AKY; ANS; AES; ADO; BSX; ALC; BTD; AALJ (Box 121/2)
  - Texas, BQR; DJU; CFW; DQO; CVC; CGM; CRS; BQY; DCL; CVE; AWU; BRF; EOG; CKN; DAI; DYO (Box 122/1)
  - Utah, AAH; DRV; AAI; DIC; DSA; DIG; AAL; CVX (Box 122/1)
  - Virginia, DHG; DJD; DVX; CYI; DGF; ANP; ELM; DGG; DTS (Box 122/1)
  - Washington, DYE; AAQ; FZ; DZR; AAN; W6334-W6352, W6672-W6676; CCI; NL (Box 122/2)
  - Wisconsin, AJA; BRN; BRS; CI; BHP; WV; WR; WS; WW (Box 122/2)
  - West Virginia, DZD; AGT; AGW; AMD; AMX; DZK; DPW (Box 122/2)
  - Wyoming, DKA; BBU; CWH; BBT; DXP; BBM; BBP; CVT (Box 122/2)
  - Whatcom County, Washington, Undated; 16DPU-4MBD480 (Box 123)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1-66 (some duplicates)
  - Northwest Washington State, 1943; L1 - L2 (Box 124)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: L1 1-32; L2 1-16
  - Northwest Washington State, 1943; L2 - L3 (Box 125)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: L2 17-32; L3 1-30
  - Northwest Washington State, 1943; L4 - L5 (Box 126)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: L4 1-31; L5 1-24
  - Northwest Washington State, 1943; L5; L5A; L6 (Box 127)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: L5 25-33; L5A 1-7; L6 1-34
  - Northwest Washington State, 1943; L7; L8 (Box 128)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: L7 1-33; L8 1-29
  - Northwest Washington State, 1943; L9; L10 (Box 129)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: L9 1-33; L10 1-31
  - Northwest Washington State, 1943; L11; L12 (Box 130)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: L11 1-35; L12 1-20
  - Northwest Washington State, 1943; L12; L13 (Box 131)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: L12 21-34; L13 1-33
  - Northwest Washington State, 1943; L14; L15 (Box 132)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: L14 1-36; L15 1-20
  - Northwest Washington State, 1943; L15; L16 (Box 133)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: L15 21-33; L16 1-35
  - Northwest Washington State, 1943; L17; L18 (Box 134)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: L17 1-33; L18 1-38
  - Washington Photo Mosaics - Washington miscellaneous northwest Sector 8-22 through 15-28, 1940s; U.S. Army Map Service (Folder P01)
    Dates on folders often listed as 1943 but may vary (circa 1940s). Not necessarily inclusive.
    Index available: Yes, in folder
  - Washington Photo Mosaics - sheets 15-20 through 18-36, circa 1943; U.S. Army Map Service (Folder P02)
  - Washington Photo Mosaics - 23-15 through 26-36, circa 1943; U.S. Army Map Service (Folder P03)
  - Washington Photo Mosaics - sheets 2-22 through 7-26, circa 1943; U.S. Army Map Service (Folder P04)
  - Washington Photo Mosaics - sheets 38-7 through 48-33, circa 1943; U.S. Army Map Service (Folder P05)
  - Washington Photo Mosaics - sheets 19-17 through 22-32, circa 1943; U.S. Army Map Service (Folder P06)
  - Washington Photo Mosaics - sheets 30-7 through 37-20, circa 1943; U.S. Army Map Service (Folder P07)
  - Washington Photo Mosaics - sheets 27-7 through 29-25, circa 1943; U.S. Army Map Service (Folder P08)
  - Whatcom County, Washington Aerial Photos, 1986; Whatcom-86 (Folder P09)
    Additional Line/Image numbers:
    10-40-2E; 11-40-2E; 14-40-2E; 15-40-2E; 16-40-2E; 21-40-2E; 22-40-2E; 23-40-2E; 26-40-2E; 27-40-2E; 28-40-2E; 32-40-2E; 34-40-2E; 35-40-2E; Dates on photos often listed as 1986, but may vary. Not necessarily inclusive.
  - Cherry Point Refinery, Washington, 1993-06-25; NSB 4-71; Geological Survey (U.S.) (Folder P10)
    2-40-3E; 3-40-3E; 4-40-3E; 5-40-3E; 9-40-3E; 10-40-3E; 14-40-3E; 15-40-3E; 16-40-3E; 17-40-3E; 21-40-3E; 22-40-3E
  - Whatcom/Skagit County, Washington (Eastern) Aerial Photographs - Various Aerial Photographs, 1950; GS-LK (Folder P11)
    includes Ross Lake, Eastern Washington
  - Lake Whatcom/‘Y’ Road/Squalicum Lake Area, Whatcom County, Washington Photo Maps, 1978-05-18; NW-78 (Folder P12)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 46B thru 59D Various
    Photos are 24”x 24”. Not necessarily inclusive.
  - Whatcom County, Washington Aerial Photographs, Unidentified; BBK (Folder P13)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 1P-30; 3P-11
    2 photos.
  - Whatcom County, Washington Aerial Photograph, Unidentified; NW-69 (Folder P14)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 106-66C-35
    1 photo.
  - Northwest Sector Maps (Whatcom, Skagit, Island and Snohomish Counties), Washington, circa 1944; War Department (Folder P15)
  - Wenatchee National Forest/Snoqualmie National Forest, Washington, 1973 (Folder P16)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 5
    With NASA index pages listed in Index Spreadsheet EEEE) Includes flight summary report.
  - Gifford Pinchot National Forest, Washington, 1972-08-05; F 70 (Folder P17)
  - Skagit County, Washington Orthophoto Various T34-36N, R4-11E, 1974-07-26; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder P18)
  - Mt. Shuksan, northeast Quadrangle 7.5 minute series, 1979; Geological Survey (U.S.) (Folder P19)
  - Lopez Island, San Juan Island (Cattle Point), San Juan County, Washington, 1941-06-27; GS S (Folder P20)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3
  - Mt. Baker Area?, 1947; GS-CJ (Folder P21)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 16
    No Township/Range on photographs
  - Fort Lewis, Washington, Grid Zone 'G', 1942; Army Corp of Engineers; Kargl Aerial Surveys (Folder P22)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 3 Photo maps 4, 7, 8 of 8 (w/dupl., 8 total)
    Scale: 1:25,000
  - Whidbey Island, Washington (Partridge Point, Penn Cove, Coupeville), (1-74, 1-84, 1-93), 1951-08-18; GS-QB (Folder P23)
  - Whidbey Island, Washington (Scatchet Head, Possession Point), (1-23, 1-51), 1952-07-02; GS-TO (Folder P23)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 2
  - Oversize Klickitat County, Washington Aerial photographs 26” x 26”, 1954-08-06; AAS-3N (Folder P24)
    Approximate image numbers: 161-200.
  - Oversize Klickitat County, Washington Aerial photographs 26” x 26, 1954-08-06; AAS-3N (Folder P25)
    Approximate image numbers: 128-177.
  - Oversize Klickitat County, Washington Aerial photographs 26” x 26, 1954-08-06; AAS-3N (Folder P26)
    Approximate image numbers: 61-126.
  - Oversize Klickitat County, Washington Aerial photographs 26” x 26, 1954-08-06; AAS-2N (Folder P27)
    Approximate image numbers: 121-127.
  - Oversize Klickitat County, Washington Aerial photographs 26” x 26, 1954-08-06; AAS-2N (Folder P28)
    Approximate image numbers: 5-49.
  - Oversize Klickitat County, Washington Aerial photographs 26” x 26, 1954-08-06; AAS-2N (Folder P29)
    Approximate image numbers: 51-119.
  - Oversize Klickitat County, Washington Aerial photographs 26” x 26, 1954-08-04; AAS-1N (Folder P30)
    Approximate image numbers: 80-169.
  - Oversize Klickitat County, Washington Aerial photographs 26” x 26, 1954-08-04; AAS-1N (Folder P31)
    Approximate image numbers: 12-78.
  - Spokane, Washington - Idaho Area 7.5 Minute Series (Liberty Lake; Greenacres; Greenacres northeast; Elk; Deer Lake; Airway Heights; Medical Lake; Spokane, northeast; Spokane, northwest), 1975-1978; Geological Survey (U.S.) (Folder P32)
  - Badger Gap, Washington Oversize Two-Sided Photo and Contour Map of Badger Gap, Washington (Yakima Firing Center), 1955; Army Map Service (Folder P33)
    Additional Line/Image numbers: 4
    Sheet 1977 IV SE AMS Series V891 andV091C; 4 Aerial photos (65-68).
  - Tomales Point/Bay, Marin County, California, 1943-10-12; COF-1B (Folder P34)
  - Northwest Whatcom County, Washington Aerial photos, undated (Folder P35)
    T38and40 Range 3E (Various sections)
  - Whatcom County, Washington Orthophoto maps, 1974 (Folder P36)
    T38-41 Ranges 1W through7E
  - Whatcom County, Washington Orthophoto maps, undated; 1974-1993; Some Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder P37)
    T40NR3E; T36 through T41 R3E through 10E
  - Whatcom County, Washington Aerial Photographs, 1971; NW-H-71 (Folder P38)
    T37 through T40; Range 3W to 6E; Includes Pt. Roberts, Washington; perhaps Skagit County.
  - Low quality Mt. Baker area “compartment Shannon” (Baker Lake, Baker Hot Springs included), Circa 1973 (Folder P39)
    Horrible condition. Includes some topo maps.
  - Point Roberts, Washington, 1950 (Folder P40)
    Extensive annotations; enlargements of photos in Box 007, folder 2.
  - Okanogan County, Washington, Aerial Photograph, 1967; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder P41)
    T40 Ranges 26-27E
  - Utah near Arizona Border photo maps, 1972 (Folder P42)
    Map showing general area and Latitude and Longitude around Zion National Park.
  - Olympic Peninsula/Hood Canal, Washington (OrthoPhoto Map), 1974; Washington (State). Department of Natural Resources. (Folder P43)
    T22N R4W